[
  {
    "Name": "Bird",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BirdFront",
      "Left": "BirdLeft",
      "Back": "BirdBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BirdFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BirdLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BirdBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Player",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PlayerFront",
      "Left": "PlayerLeft",
      "Back": "PlayerBack",
      "FrontMoving": "PlayerFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "PlayerLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "PlayerBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "GrassPokemon",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "GrassPokemonFront",
      "Left": "GrassPokemonLeft",
      "Back": "GrassPokemonBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NormalPokemon",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NormalPokemonFront",
      "Left": "NormalPokemonLeft",
      "Back": "NormalPokemonBack",
      "FrontMoving": "NormalPokemonFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "NormalPokemonLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "NormalPokemonBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "LtSurge",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "LtSurgeFront",
      "Left": "LtSurgeLeft",
      "Back": "LtSurgeBack",
      "FrontMoving": "LtSurgeFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "LtSurgeLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "LtSurgeBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "TeamRocket",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "TeamRocketFront",
      "Left": "TeamRocketLeft",
      "Back": "TeamRocketBack",
      "FrontMoving": "TeamRocketFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "TeamRocketLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "TeamRocketBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Lance",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "LanceFront",
      "Left": "LanceLeft",
      "Back": "LanceBack",
      "FrontMoving": "LanceFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "LanceLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "LanceBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Bruno",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BrunoFront",
      "Left": "BrunoLeft",
      "Back": "BrunoBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BrunoFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BrunoLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BrunoBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "BlackBelt",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BlackBeltFront",
      "Left": "BlackBeltLeft",
      "Back": "BlackBeltBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BlackBeltFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BlackBeltLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BlackBeltBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Giovanni",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "GiovanniFront",
      "Left": "GiovanniLeft",
      "Back": "GiovanniBack",
      "FrontMoving": "GiovanniFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "GiovanniLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "GiovanniBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Cook",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "CookFront",
      "Left": "CookLeft",
      "Back": "CookBack",
      "FrontMoving": "CookFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "CookLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "CookBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Jessie",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "JessieFront",
      "Left": "JessieLeft",
      "Back": "JessieBack",
      "FrontMoving": "JessieFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "JessieLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "JessieBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "James",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "JamesFront",
      "Left": "JamesLeft",
      "Back": "JamesBack",
      "FrontMoving": "JamesFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "JamesLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "JamesBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "ProfOak",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ProfOakFront",
      "Left": "ProfOakLeft",
      "Back": "ProfOakBack",
      "FrontMoving": "ProfOakFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "ProfOakLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "ProfOakBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Kyio",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "KyioFront",
      "Left": "KyioLeft",
      "Back": "KyioBack",
      "FrontMoving": "KyioFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "KyioLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "KyioBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Swimmer",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SwimmerFront",
      "Left": "SwimmerLeft",
      "Back": "SwimmerBack",
      "FrontMoving": "SwimmerFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "SwimmerLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "SwimmerBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "WaterPokemon",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "WaterPokemonFront",
      "Left": "WaterPokemonLeft",
      "Back": "WaterPokemonBack",
      "FrontMoving": "WaterPokemonFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "WaterPokemonLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "WaterPokemonBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Jenny",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "JennyFront",
      "Left": "JennyLeft",
      "Back": "JennyBack",
      "FrontMoving": "JennyFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "JennyLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "JennyBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Erika",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ErikaFront",
      "Left": "ErikaLeft",
      "Back": "ErikaBack",
      "FrontMoving": "ErikaFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "ErikaLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "ErikaBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Mother",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "MotherFront",
      "Left": "MotherLeft",
      "Back": "MotherBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "PlayerBike",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PlayerBikeFront",
      "Left": "PlayerBikeLeft",
      "Back": "PlayerBikeBack",
      "FrontMoving": "PlayerBikeFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "PlayerBikeLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "PlayerBikeBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Biker",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BikerFront",
      "Left": "BikerLeft",
      "Back": "BikerBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BikerFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BikerLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BikerBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Sailor",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SailorFront",
      "Left": "SailorLeft",
      "Back": "SailorBack",
      "FrontMoving": "SailorFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "SailorLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "SailorBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Pika",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PikaFront",
      "Left": "PikaLeft",
      "Back": "PikaBack",
      "FrontMoving": "PikaFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "PikaLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "PikaBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Lorelie",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "LorelieFront",
      "Left": "LorelieLeft",
      "Back": "LorelieBack",
      "FrontMoving": "LorelieFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "LorelieLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "LorelieBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Sabrina",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SabrinaFront",
      "Left": "SabrinaLeft",
      "Back": "SabrinaBack",
      "FrontMoving": "SabrinaFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "SabrinaLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "SabrinaBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Daisy",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "DaisyFront",
      "Left": "DaisyLeft",
      "Back": "DaisyBack",
      "FrontMoving": "DaisyFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "DaisyLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "DaisyBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Jigglypuff",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "JigglypuffFront",
      "Left": "JigglypuffLeft",
      "Back": "JigglypuffBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Rival",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "RivalFront",
      "Left": "RivalLeft",
      "Back": "RivalBack",
      "FrontMoving": "RivalFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "RivalLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "RivalBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "OldMan",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "OldManFront",
      "Left": "OldManLeft",
      "Back": "OldManBack",
      "FrontMoving": "OldManFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "OldManLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "OldManBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Gentleman",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "GentlemanFront",
      "Left": "GentlemanLeft",
      "Back": "GentlemanBack",
      "FrontMoving": "GentlemanFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "GentlemanLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "GentlemanBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Sandshrew",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "Tile315",
      "Left": "Tile460",
      "Back": "Tile393",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NameRater",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NameRaterFront",
      "Left": "NameRaterLeft",
      "Back": "NameRaterBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "SurferPika",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SurferPikaFront",
      "Left": "SurferPikaLeft",
      "Back": "SurferPikaBack",
      "FrontMoving": "SurferPikaFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "SurferPikaLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "SurferPikaBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Pokeball",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PokeballFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Rock",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "RockFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Reina",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ReinaFront",
      "Left": "ReinaLeft",
      "Back": "ReinaBack",
      "FrontMoving": "ReinaFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "ReinaLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "ReinaBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Assistant",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "AssistantFront",
      "Left": "AssistantLeft",
      "Back": "AssistantBack",
      "FrontMoving": "AssistantFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "AssistantLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "AssistantBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Aghata",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "AghataFront",
      "Left": "AghataLeft",
      "Back": "AghataBack",
      "FrontMoving": "AghataFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "AghataLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "AghataBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Channeler",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ChannelerFront",
      "Left": "ChannelerLeft",
      "Back": "ChannelerBack",
      "FrontMoving": "ChannelerFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "ChannelerLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "ChannelerBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "MrFuji",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "MrFujiFront",
      "Left": "MrFujiLeft",
      "Back": "MrFujiBack",
      "FrontMoving": "MrFujiFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "MrFujiLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "MrFujiBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Brock",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BrockFront",
      "Left": "BrockLeft",
      "Back": "BrockBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BrockFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BrockLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BrockBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Blaine",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "Tile327",
      "Left": "Tile480",
      "Back": "Tile399",
      "FrontMoving": "Tile525",
      "LeftMoving": "BaldGuyLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BigGuyBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Bill",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BillFront",
      "Left": "BillLeft",
      "Back": "BillBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BillFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BillLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BillBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "CopyCat",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "CopyCatFront",
      "Left": "CopyCatLeft",
      "Back": "CopyCatBack",
      "FrontMoving": "CopyCatFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "CopyCatLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "CopyCatBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Snorlax",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SnorlaxFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "SafariZoneWarden",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "SafariZoneWardenFront",
      "Left": "SafariZoneWardenLeft",
      "Back": "SafariZoneWardenBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Koga",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "KogaFront",
      "Left": "KogaLeft",
      "Back": "KogaBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Fisher",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "FisherFront",
      "Left": "FisherLeft",
      "Back": "FisherBack",
      "FrontMoving": "FisherFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "FisherLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "FisherBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Bulbasaur",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BulbasaurFront",
      "Left": "BulbasaurLeft",
      "Back": "BulbasaurBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Beauty",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BeautyFront",
      "Left": "BeautyLeft",
      "Back": "BeautyBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BeautyFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BeautyLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BeautyBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "BugCatcher",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BugCatcherFront",
      "Left": "BugCatcherLeft",
      "Back": "BugCatcherBack",
      "FrontMoving": "BugCatcherFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "BugCatcherLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "BugCatcherBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Lass",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "LassFront",
      "Left": "LassLeft",
      "Back": "LassBack",
      "FrontMoving": "LassFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "LassLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "LassBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Clefairy",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ClefairyFront",
      "Left": "ClefairyLeft",
      "Back": "ClefairyBack",
      "FrontMoving": "ClefairyFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "ClefairyLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "ClefairyBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Wigglytuff ",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "Wigglytuff Front",
      "Left": "Wigglytuff Left",
      "Back": "Wigglytuff Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Chansey",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "ChanseyFront",
      "Left": "ChanseyLeft",
      "Back": "ChanseyBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Bug",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BugFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": "BugFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Normal",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NormalFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": "NormalFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "FlowerPokemon",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "FlowerPokemonFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": "FlowerPokemonFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Fossil",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "FossilFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "GymGuide",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "GymGuideFront",
      "Left": "GymGuideLeft",
      "Back": "GymGuideBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale1",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale1Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale1Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale1Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCOld1",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCOld1Front",
      "Left": "NPCOld1Left",
      "Back": "NPCOld1Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale2",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale2Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale2Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale2Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale3",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale3Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale3Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale3Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale4",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale4Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale4Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale4Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCFemale1",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCFemale1Front",
      "Left": "NPCFemale1Left",
      "Back": "NPCFemale1Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCChild1",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCChild1Front",
      "Left": "NPCChild1Left",
      "Back": "NPCChild1Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale5",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale5Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale5Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale5Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Police",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PoliceFront",
      "Left": "PoliceLeft",
      "Back": "PoliceBack",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCChild2",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCChild2Front",
      "Left": "NPCChild2Left",
      "Back": "NPCChild2Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Pokefan",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PokefanFront",
      "Left": "PokefanLeft",
      "Back": "PokefanBack",
      "FrontMoving": "PokefanFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "PokefanLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "PokefanBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale6",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale6Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale6Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale6Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "NPCMale7",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NPCMale7Front",
      "Left": "NPCMale7Left",
      "Back": "NPCMale7Back",
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Guard",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "GuardFront",
      "Left": "GuardLeft",
      "Back": "GuardBack",
      "FrontMoving": "GuardFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": "GuardLeftMoving",
      "BackMoving": "GuardBackMoving"
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "PoisonPokemon",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PoisonPokemonFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": "PoisonPokemonFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "OldManLying",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "OldManLyingFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Paper",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "PaperFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Book",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "BookFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Note",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NoteFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Coin",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "CoinFront",
      "Left": null,
      "Back": null,
      "FrontMoving": null,
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  },
  {
    "Name": "Nurse",
    "Mappings": {
      "Front": "NurseFront",
      "Left": "NurseLeft",
      "Back": "NurseBack",
      "FrontMoving": "NurseFrontMoving",
      "LeftMoving": null,
      "BackMoving": null
    }
  }
]